tastyquery.com 2019-05-19

# Terms of use and privacy policy - Tasty Query

### §1

Whenever in these regulations are the following concepts, there must be understood as follows:

**Regulations** \- these regulations of use Tasty Query.

**Service** \- Tasty Query, a website presenting food blogs and publishing their content, which is located at http://tastyquery.com and all the features and tools available through this website.

**User** \- a person with full legal capacity, which through acceptance of Regulations gained access to the service specified in §2 of Regulations. The user may also be a natural person and/or not having full legal capacity, provided to the consent of the legal representative.

### §2

Regulations define the implementation rules for the Website Users, services provided by electronic means, which is to enable service users to become familiar with the blogs index, search blogs, adding to the index of new blogs and participate in campaigns.

### §3

Within the framework of the electronically supplied services available to Users is software that enables the use of the services referred to § 2, under the conditions established by the provisions of these Regulations.

### §4

All content published on the websites of the blogs are on the sole responsibility of the bloggers and blogs comments authors. The sole responsibility for the content bear their authors.

### §5

It is unacceptable to take on the Website acts contrary to the law, widely considered morally reprehensible, socially inappropriate or violating the rules of Netiquette, in particular, it is unacceptable:

  * adding the users to blogs index and setting up the culinary campaigns containing illegal content, calling for racial hatred, religious, ethnic, or glorifies violence, as well as blogs and campaigns with content widely recognized as morally reprehensible, socially inappropriate and in violation of the rules of Netiquette,
  * adding by the Users to blogs index and campaigns recipes that contain text materials, graphics, audio, multimedia or audiovisual violating the law protected the good of others.

### §6

The condition of adding a blog to the Website index is putting on it designation as a Website logo and link to the Website home page.

### §7

Website reserves the right to refuse to add a blog to the index, especially when the content of this blog are not related to the subject or for other reasons.

### §8

In case of violation of the §6 of these Regulations, the user will lose the full functionality of the Website.Ultimately, blogs, and culinary campaigns can be removed from the index, particularly in the case of violations of their authors provisions of §5 of these Regulations or when the blog ceases to fulfill the conditions laid down in Article §7 of the Regulations.

### §9

Based on the applicable law, data of the Website Users may be transferred to the court, the prosecutor's office, the police and other competent authorities on the needs of their investigations.

### §10

Website will make every effort to ensure proper operation, uptime and availability around the clock and provide assistance in resolving problems relating to its operation. But does not guarantee connectivity and reserves the right to suspend provision of the Website for technical reasons.

### §11

  1. The presented Regulations may amend.
  2. Subject to the provisions of paragraphs. 3 of this article and provided no submission by the User statement there indicated, all changes are effective from the date indicated in the revised Regulations, which the day may not be earlier than the publication date of the amended Regulations on the Website.
  3. Within 7 days from the publication date of the amended Regulations User may submit a statement of disagreement to be in force in relation to it amended the Regulations - such a statement will be treated as a termination by the user of the legal relationship giving rise to the provision of services referred to in §2 of these Regulations.
  4. In the case of the statement referred to in paragraph. 3 above, service in relation to the User ceases to be provided within 3 working days from the date of submission by the User statement.
  5. The statement referred to in paragraph. 3 of this section for its effectiveness should be submitted to the appropriate Website subpage.

### §12

  1. Website Users personal data will be processed in order to provide the services referred to in §2.
  2. You have the right to inspect yours personal data and correct them.
  3. Providing personal data is voluntary.
  4. Privacy policy defines the terms and conditions Privacy Policy available below: 
    1. What data we collect about you? 
      * To be able to take advantage of the features offered by the service you have to register. During registration, we will ask you for your e-mail address and password, which you will be using on our website.
      * During Your visit to our website, automatically collects data about Your visit, such as your IP address, domain name, browser type, operating system type, etc.
      * When you contact us via the website, phone, e-mail, etc., you give us your personal information, such as your name, surname, e-mail, etc.
    2. How we use your data? 
      * In any case, we will not sell the data collected about You to third parties.
      * Data collected during registration will be used only to allow You to log in to the Website. Registration is compulsory if you want to use the features offered by the Website.
      * Data collected automatically can be used to analyse users behaviour on our website, gather demographic information about our users, or to personalise the content of our webpages. These data are collected automatically for each user.
      * Data collected in the course of correspondence between You and our Website will be used only to respond to Your request.
      * In the case of the control of the General Inspectorate for Personal Data Protection, Your data can be made available to employees of the Inspectorate in accordance with the Act on Personal Data Protection.
      * In case of violation of the website Regulations, violations of law, or when they are required by law, we may disclose Your information to the judicial authorities.
      * The data are processed in a manner consistent with the scope provided by the User and the requirements of the law.
    3. How can we contact you? 
      * You can receive our e-mails containing important information relating to the Website.
      * If you have subscribed to receive automatic notifications of the Website, you will receive them from us by e-mail.
    4. How can you tell us about the change of data? 
      * After logging into the system and selecting the My Data, you can make changes or delete your personal information collected during registration and is used to log into the system. Automatically collected data cannot be changed or removed.
    5. The use of cookies. 
      * Our website may use cookies to identify Your browser while using our website, so that we know which page to display. Cookies do not contain any personal data. Detailed information about cookies can be found on the page.
    6. How do we protect Your personal data? 
      * The security of your personal data is our highest priority. Our databases are protected from unauthorized disclosure to third parties, use, alteration and destruction.
    7. Outbound links 
      * On the Website you can find links to allow direct access to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policy applied by the owners of those sites. We encourage you to familiarise yourself with the contents of privacy statements on websites that collect personal information.
    8. Contact us 
      * If you have any further questions about privacy, please send them to the address, the appropriate form can be found on the Contact page.
